jqueryhouse.com 2019-04-16

# jQueryHouse Privacy Statement | jQueryHouse

## Your privacy is critically important to us.

  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

## Website Visitors

Like most website operators, jQuery House collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. jQuery House’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how jQuery House’s visitors use its website.

jQuery House also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users.

## Ads and Third Party Cookies

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site including cookies. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

## Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. jQuery House uses cookies to help jQuery House identify and track visitors, their usage of jQuery House website, and their website access preferences. jQuery House visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using jQuery House’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of jQuery House’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, jQuery House may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in jQuery House’s sole discretion. jQuery House encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
